celebtaboo.com 2010-12-21

# Our Commitment To Privacy

**Privacy Policy Statement**

This website ("We, "Us", or the "Site") is governed by the following privacy policy. 

**Contact Information**

_Customer Support_ ,  
The Site can be reached via e-mail at [cs@celebtaboo.com](mailto:cs@celebtaboo.com)

**Terms of Use/ Consent**

By using this Site and/or volunteering information you are giving your express consent to the Site's privacy policy as outlined in this document. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site 

**Personal Information**

Personal information may include such information as your name, email address, mailing addresses, birthdates and information collected electronically via cookies. 

**What we collect**

The Site collects personal information when you register for The Site, when you visit The Site's pages, when you contact the Site, or any of its employees, agents or representatives, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. 

When you register we ask you for personal information such as your name, address, email address, telephone number and mobile phone number. Once you register and log in to the member area, you are not anonymous to us. 

The Site automatically collects and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your [IP Address](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/I/IP_address.html), [cookie](http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/c/cookie.html) information, and the page(s) you request. 

Uses of Personal Information - Why We collect it? 

The Site uses personal information for the following general purposes: 

  1. to customize the advertising and content you see;
  2. fulfill your requests for products and services;
  3. improve our services;
  4. contact you;
  5. conduct research; and,
  6. provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

By providing your personal information to this Site, you are expressly consenting to the use or disclosure of your personal information by the Site for the purposes stated above and in the manner that it sees fit. 

This site may share your personal information including your IP Address, your e-mail address with its affiliates and third parties. 

The Site may also share information when we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of The Site's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

The Site may transfer information about you if The Site is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, if this transfer subjects you to a different privacy policy, The Site will notify you before information about you is transferred. 

**Third Party Links from our Site**

We do not provide any personal information to any third parties without your permission. 

Third Party Web service providers may have advertising banners and/or links on the Site. The Site is not responsible or liable for the use of any information that a consumer may provide, or that is gathered by third-party websites that have banner ads or links on the Site.   
This Site does not control, monitor or endorse the information gathering practices or Privacy Policies of any of those third-party websites. Whenever applicable, each consumer should seek to read the Privacy Policy of any third-party website provider that has an advertising banner, advertises or has a link on the Site. 

**Security of Personal Information Collected by the Site**

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. All consumers should consider any information provided to or collected by the Site as non-confidential, and consequently the Site assumes no liability or responsibility if any information relating to any consumer is intercepted and/or used by an unintended recipient. 

**Review of Personal Information by you/Means of Challenging Data**

The Data Controller for all personal information collected can be reached by e-mail at [privacy@celebtaboo.com](mailto:privacy@celebtaboo.com). The Data Controller has the authority to resolve all issues regarding the collection, modification, correction, deletion and use of the personal information that has been collected by the Site. 

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy or if you feel that the personal information is inaccurate or incomplete, you may e-mail the Site's Data Controller at [privacy@celebtaboo.com](mailto:privacy@celebtaboo.com). 

**Changes to this Policy**

From time to time, the Site may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes. It is your responsibility to review these changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please contact the Data Controller by e-mail at [privacy@celebtaboo.com](mailto:privacy@celebtaboo.com).  
Above all, you alone are responsible for keeping your information safe. Be careful and responsible whenever you're online.
